A Guide to the Dept. of Employment Dispute Resolution Agency Head Correspondence and Subject Files, 1980-2012
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Dept. of Employment Dispute Resolution Agency Head Correspondence and Subject Files, 1980-2012
The Library of Virginia
33519, 36360, 43552, 44014, 50472, 51872
60 cu. ft.
Dept. of Employment Dispute Resolution
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Privacy protected and other protected information is considered confidential and restricted from public access for 75 years (Code of Virginia 42.1-78). Types of information that may be restricted include but are not limited to: Personal information (2.2-3801); Personnel records (2.2-3705.1; Grievability and compliance ruling files - Administrative investigations (2.2-3705.3). It is necessary for an archivist to review any unprocessed, modern record collections (those collections less than 75 years old) that may contain privacy protected or confidential information before the records can be used by patrons for research purposes or before any copies can be made. If you are planning to use these records, please contact Archives Reference Services for more details before planning your research trip.
Acquisition Information
Accession 33519 transferred by Dept. of Employment Dispute Resolution, 31 August 1989.
Accession 36360 transferred by Dept. of Employment Dispute Resolution, 19 February 1999.
Accession 43552 transferred by Dept. of Employment Dispute Resolution, 03 December 2007.
Accession 44014 transferred by Dept. of Employment Dispute Resolution, 17 November 2008.
Accession 50472 transferred by Dept. of Employment Dispute Resolution, 25 June 2012.
Accession 51872 transferred by Dept. of Human Resource Management, 15 July 2016.
Historical Information
The Dept. of Employment Dispute Resolution was created by an act which passed the General Assembly on 10 March 1978 coinciding with the establishment of a new grievance procedure for state employees.
Scope and Content
These records consist of agency head correspondence, and may include reports and copies of grievability rulings. These files document the planning, direction, and implementation of agency programs and are evidence of actions and policy decisions.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged into one series: Agency head correspondence and subject files, 1980-2012.
Contents List
- Agency head correspondence and subject files, 1980-2006.
  - Accession 33519, 1984-1985.
    This accession is contained within one box, possessing 24 folders arranged chronologically by month.
  - Accession 36360, 1986-1993.
    This accession is arranged in chronological order.
    - January-December 1986. (Box 1)
    - 1987. (Box 2)
    - June-December 1988. (Box 3)
    - January-May 1988. (Box 4)
    - Jan-June 1989. (Box 5)
    - July-December 1989. (Box 6)
    - 1990. (Box 7)
    - 1991. (Box 8)
    - January-December 1992. (Box 9)
    - January-December 1993. (Box 10)
  - Accession 43552, 1980-2006.
    This accession is arranged according to subject, with no clear alphabetical or chronological order.
    - #3--Dept. of General Services, July 1, 1998. (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - "A", 1995-1996. (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Acting Director, 1994. (Box 18, Folder 24)
    - Ad Comparisons, 1991. (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - ADA, 1996. (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - ADA; Court Cases: Miller, B., Champ, J.W., Rucker, M., 1997. (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Administrative Hearing Officers #1, 1994. (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Administrative Hearing Officers #2, 1996. (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - ADR World.com, May 2002. (Box 24, Folder 30)
    - Ads--Recruitment Copies, 2001. (Box 22, Folder 25)
    - Advice Line Costs, FY2000. (Box 15, Folder 25)
    - Aeropark, 1998. (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Age Discrimination, 1996. (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Agee, Christina, 2001. (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Agency Energy Manager Training, June 10, 1999. (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Agency Head Subject Files, 1986-1991. (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Agency Head Subject Files, 1995. (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Agency Head Transmittal, 2001. (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Agency Legislation Session, 2001. (Box 24, Folder 23)
    - Agency Personnel Listings, 1992. (Box 18, Folder 25)
    - Agency Reconciliation to DOA Reports, July 21, 2000. (Box 15, Folder 30)
    - Agency Regulatory Coordinator-Virginia Register of Regulation, 2000. (Box 7, Folder 51)
    - Agreement between Dept. of Aging and DERC (loaned employee, 1992. (Box 18, Folder 56)
    - Agreement between SWVTC and DERC Mediation Skills and non-Supervisory Training, January 1997-June 1997. (Box 29, Folder 31)
    - AHO Bills, FY 1987-1988. (Box 18, Folder 55)
    - AHO Conference, March 1-3 1998. (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - AHO Conference, September 9-11 1998. (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Air Travel Card, 1997. (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - American Express Card Billing Information, 1997. (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - American Express at Work, 2001. (Box 7, Folder 34)
    - Americans with Disabilities Act, April 9, 1996. (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Americans with Disabilities Act (Questions and Answers--EEOC), 1997. (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - Annual Contingency Plan Survey, 1992. (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Annual Guidance Document List, December 1998. (Box 20, Folder 21)
    - Annual Guidance Document List, December 1998. (Box 20, Folder 29)
    - Annual Report, 1996. (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Annual Reports, Requests for, 1997. (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Applications for Employment (Miscellaneous), 1996. (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Approvals for Hiring, 1995. (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Audit of WTA, 1997. (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Auditor of Public Accounts, 1997. (Box 18, Folder 42)
    - B, 1998. (Box 27, Folder 21)
    - Background Materials, 1997. (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - Back Pay, n.d.. (Box 27, Folder 22)
    - Back-up to Budget Work, 1998. (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - Best Practices in Discipline and Termination, n.d.. (Box 7, Folder 41)
    - Bill Under First A., 1996. (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Bolling, Eugene: Letter, 2001. (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Books and Publications Ordered, 1994. (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - Bowser, Charles, 1998. (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Brown, Jeff (ERC applicant), 1999. (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Buckingham Greenery Inter-Landscapes, December 1999. (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - Budget Drafts, September 21, 1998. (Box 20, Folder 19)
    - Budget File, 2000. (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - Budget and Operating Correspondence, 1998-1999. (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Burtch, Jack W., Jr., March 12, 1996. (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Bus Tickets--GRTC, 1995-1996. (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Business Card Orders, 2000. (Box 7, Folder 44)
    - "C", 1988-1990. (Box 27, Folder 23)
    - Calendar Orders, 1998. (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - CAPP--Manual Correspondence, 1996. (Box 18, Folder 40)
    - Carter, Anita, 1983. (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - Cell Phone--EDR Information, 2003. (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - Cell Phones and Pager Information, 2002. (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Certificates of Coverage, 1990. (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Challenges Summary, March 23, 2004. (Box 20, Folder 33)
    - CIM, 1993-1995. (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - CIM Correspondance, 1995. (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - CIM Inventory, 1995. (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - CIPPS, 1995. (Box 18, Folder 39)
    - Circuit Court Filing Fees, 1994. (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Circuit Court Panel Appointments, 1990. (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - City of Hampton--Dept. of Human Resources, September 7, 1993. (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Class and Comp, 1994. (Box 18, Folder 49)
    - Classification of Consultant Positions, 2000. (Box 12, Folder 32)
    - Classified Compensation Plan, 2000. (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - Closing Procedures, FY2000. (Box 15, Folder 29)
    - Code Adam Alerts in Public Buildings, 2003. (Box 24, Folder 17)
    - Colleges, 1997. (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Commercial Activity Inventory, 1999. (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Commission on Human Rights, 1987. (Box 28, Folder 19)
    - Commodity Class/Assignments, 1997. (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - Common Law Torts in Workplace, n.d.. (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - Commonwealth Competition Council, November 14, 1996. (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Commonwealth Competition Council, 1997. (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - Commonwealth Currents, 1996-1997. (Box 18, Folder 45)
    - Commonwealth Management Institute, 1997. (Box 27, Folder 15)
    - Community College System, Virginia, 1998. (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - Community Mediation Center, 1999. (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Community Work Experience Program (CWEP)--DSS, November 1995. (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - Compensation Pilots, 1996. (Box 27, Folder 18)
    - Compensation Reform File, 2000. (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - Compensation Reform--Main File, 2000. (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - Compensation Reform Training Performance Management, November 2000. (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Compliance Review by DOA, 1995. (Box 18, Folder 41)
    - Computer Bucks--VPSI, Inc., 1999. (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Computer Purchases, October 1999. (Box 12, Folder 35)
    - Computer Purchases--Computers, May 2000. (Box 12, Folder 34)
    - Computer Purchases--Computer Projectors, April 2000. (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Computer Purchases--HP 4050 TN Laser Printers, April 2000. (Box 12, Folder 33)
    - Computer Purchases--HP Scanner, January 2000. (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Computer Purchases--XEROX Personal Laser Printers, January 2000. (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Computer Software Notes, 1991. (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Computer Training, 1999. (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Conference Call Forms, n.d.. (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Conflict of Interest Filing, 1999. (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Conflict of Interests Act (Virginia), 1993-1994. (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Conformity of Grievance Procedures, 1990. (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Constitutional Officers, 1993. (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Construction Issues, May-June 2000. (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Contact Records, 1999. (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Contract #962-97-4--Mediation Training, May 1, 1998-April 30, 2000. (Box 29, Folder 29)
    - Contract Masters List, 1998. (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - Copyright Services--Jay Jenkins, Copywriter, 1997. (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - Council on Human Rights Interview Panel Applications, 1999. (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Council on Information Management, 1994. (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Council on Information Management, 1996. (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Council on Information Management Correspondence and Booklets, 1991. (Box 24, Folder 33)
    - Counselor Recruitment, December 1998. (Box 20, Folder 24)
    - Countiss, April; Roark, Peggy, 1999. (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - CVC, 2003. (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - CWA--Public and Health Care Workers, 1992. (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - "D"--Data Dictionary, 1997. (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Debarred Vendors, 1998. (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - Demographics of Workplace, 1996. (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Dept. of Corrections, 1998. (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Dept. for Deaf and Hard of Hearing, 1987. (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Dept. of Health, 1996. (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Dept. of Information Technology, 1991. (Box 24, Folder 34)
    - Dept. of Information Technology, 1995-1998. (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Dept. of Information Technology, 1999. (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - Dept. of Personnel and Training, 1997. (Box 14, Folder 30)
    - Dept. of Personnel and Training, 1997. (Box 18, Folder 46)
    - Dept. of Personnel and Training, 1998. (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - Dept. of Personnel and Training, 1998. (Box 14, Folder 27)
    - Dept. of Personnel and Training Administrative Correspondence, 1994. (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Dept. of Personnel and Training Classified Employee/Position Exclusion Listing, 1995. (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - Dept. of Planning and Budget, 1996. (Box 18, Folder 53)
    - Dept. of Rehabilitative Services, 1995. (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - DERC--"776" Employees, 1995. (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - DERC--Annual Reports, 1981-1996. (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - DERC--Annual Report, 1995. (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - DERC--Annual Report, 1997. (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - DERC--Annual Report, 1998. (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - DERC Brochure--possible changes, 1993. (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - DERC--Budget Proposals and Expenditures, 1998-1999. (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - DERC Bulletins, July 1, 1995. (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - DERC--Contracts, 1999. (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - DERC--DPT IPP Training, April-May 1993. (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - DERC--EEO and Affirmative Action, 1997. (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - DERC--EEO Feasibility Study, 1983. (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - DERC--Employee Assistance Program, 1981. (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - DERC--Energy Plan, FY 1998-1999. (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - DERC--Energy Plan, 1999. (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - DERC--Equipment, 1991-1995. (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - DERC--Fax Numbers, 1996. (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - DERC--HRM Survey--Section 10, 1989. (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - DERC--Interns (Law Students), 1999. (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - DERC--Invoices and Correspondence, 1996-1997. (Box 29, Folder 32)
    - DERC--Logos, n.d.. (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - DERC--to Mail, 1997. (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - DERC--Newsletters, FY 1988-1989. (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - DERC--Open House, December 6, 1999. (Box 15, Folder 33)
    - DERC--Organizational and Budget Information, 1993. (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - DERC Organizational Chart by Position Number, 1996. (Box 18, Folder 28)
    - DERC--Organization Charts, April 2000. (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - DERC--P-5's, 1997. (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - DERC--Performance Measures, 1993. (Box 18, Folder 31)
    - DERC--Personnel Agency Mission Statement, October 15, 1997. (Box 18, Folder 43)
    - DERC--Plan for 3-Step Increase, 1998. (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - DERC--Pocket Folders, May 1998. (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - DERC--Poster, 1997. (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - DERC--Project Memos, 1990-1996. (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - DERC--Publication Costs, 1988-1998. (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - DERC--Reorganization, 1986. (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - DERC--Staff Meetings, 1999. (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - DERC--Staff Schedule, 1996. (Box 18, Folder 27)
    - DERC--Staff Training Schedules/Information, 1998. (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - DERC--Strategic Plan, October 24, 1997. (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - DERC--Strategic Plan, 2000-2002. (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - DERC--Telephone Calling Cards, 1994. (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - DERC--Telephone Directory Listings, 1997. (Box 5, Folder 46)
    - DERC--Transit Incentive Pilot, 1995. (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - DERC--Videotape, 1988. (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Dering, Leslie--Contract Issue, 1995. (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Developing Your Agency's RTW Policy, April 24, 2001. (Box 22, Folder 22)
    - DGS, 1991. (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - DGS--Fiscal Notes, 1994. (Box 18, Folder 34)
    - DGS Fiscal Reports and FAACS Information, 2002. (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - DGS Policy on Use of State Meeting Rooms by Nonstate or Nonprofit, 1997. (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - DGS--Virginia Distribution Center, 2001. (Box 5, Folder 50)
    - Disability, 1996. (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Dishwasher, 1997. (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - DIT--Cell Phone, 1998. (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - D.I.T. File, 2000. (Box 24, Folder 26)
    - DIT Information, 2002. (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - DIT--Phone Bill, October 2000. (Box 7, Folder 43)
    - DIT--Security Access, 1993. (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - DIT--TSR, 2000. (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - DIT--Website Information, 1999. (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - Division of Hearings, 2000. (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Division of Unclaimed Property Report, 2001. (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - DLAS Book, 1995. (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - DLS-Liaison Officers, 2001. (Box 7, Folder 49)
    - DOA, 1999. (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - DOA, 2000. (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - DOA Contracts, 1999. (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - DOC Academy for Staff Development--Crozier, Virginia, December 3, 1998. (Box 20, Folder 22)
    - Documents Used in Preparation for Budget Submission, 1997. (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - DOH Activity Codes, 2001. (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - DPT Benefits Study--Personnel Series, 1994. (Box 18, Folder 50)
    - DPT Compensation Plan Reform Committee, 1989. (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - DPT--Draft Policies, 1996. (Box 18, Folder 44)
    - DPT--forms, 1993. (Box 18, Folder 47)
    - DPT Interpretations, 1998. (Box 14, Folder 28)
    - DPT Salary Adjustment Policy, January 7, 1999. (Box 14, Folder 26)
    - DPT Training Schedules, 1998. (Box 14, Folder 29)
    - Drafts for Secretary, 1998. (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Drug-Free Workplace Act Certification, 1993. (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - DSIA Survey, 1998. (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Dukane LCD Projector, 1995. (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - "E", 1998. (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - EA Meeting, June 2, 2004. (Box 20, Folder 36)
    - Early Retirement, FY 1992. (Box 12, Folder 31)
    - EDR Compensation Reform Planning Checklist (Henderson File), 2000. (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - EDR/DHRM Sept. 2000 Meeting, Sept. 2000. (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - EDR Emergency Action Plan, August 14, 2003. (Box 20, Folder 32)
    - EDR/HRM Information Exchange, July 20, 2000. (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - EDR Performance Measures, 1997-2000. (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - EDR Salary Administrative Plan, December 1, 2000. (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - EDR Website, 2000. (Box 7, Folder 48)
    - EDR's Emergency Action Plan, 2001. (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - EDR's Legislation, 2002. (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - EDR's Proposed Legislation, 2003. (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - EDR's Proposed Legislation, 2003. (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - EDR's Proposed Legislative Amendments for 2001 Legislative Session, August 2000. (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - EDR's SAP Revision, 2002. (Box 24, Folder 29)
    - EDR's Workplace Violence Policy, 2003. (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - EEO, 1998. (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - EEO Report, 1992-1993. (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - E-Government and Seat Man. Information, 2001. (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Employee Demographics, 1998. (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Employee Grievance Procedure--Correspondence and Draft, 1994-1997. (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - Employee Handbook, n.d.. (Box 5, Folder 37)
    - Employee Leaves of Absence, October 8, 1996. (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Employee Notice Poster Order Forms, 1997. (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Employee Notice Posters/Correspondence, 1997. (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Employee Notice Requirements, 1997. (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Employee Outreach Project, 1992. (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Employee Productivity Incentive Fund, July 17, 1992. (Box 29, Folder 25)
    - Employee Recognition Program Information, February 16, 2001. (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - Employee Relations Management Evaluation Handbook--DPT, 1994. (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - Employee Safety Program, 1994. (Box 5, Folder 38)
    - Employee Suggestion Program, 1993. (Box 14, Folder 31)
    - Employee Suggestion Program, 1994-2002. (Box 14, Folder 32)
    - Employees' Handbook--DPT, 1987. (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - Energy Plan, 1999-2000. (Box 7, Folder 38)
    - Equal Employment Opportunity Commission (U.S.), 1997. (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Established Positions Report, 1996. (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - EVA Procurement Implementation, 2002. (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - Executive Agreements, 1984. (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Exemption Forms and Requests to Hire, 1995. (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Expired Data Sheets, 1996. (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - "F", 1996. (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Fair Labor Standards Act, February 13, 1996. (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Family and Medical Leave Act, 1993-1997. (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - Farr, Claudia; Logan, Michelle; Lauderdale, Michael, 1999. (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - FATS, 1992. (Box 18, Folder 38)
    - FATS, 1993. (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - FATS--forms, n.d.. (Box 18, Folder 37)
    - FATS--Probud, 1994. (Box 18, Folder 36)
    - Federal Express Air, 1996. (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - Federal Surplus Property Authorization, 2001. (Box 7, Folder 42)
    - Fiscal--General Correspondence, 1996. (Box 18, Folder 35)
    - Flex-time Schedules, 1997. (Box 18, Folder 23)
    - Flexible Reimbursement Account Information, 1998. (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - FLSA, 1995. (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - FLSA--Reimbursements, 1996. (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - FMLA, 1993. (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - FMLA, 1997. (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - FMLA Cases, 1995. (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - FMLA (DERC), 1999. (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Form Letters, 2000. (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - Form Letters (samples), 1998. (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Fraud Abuse Hotline, 1994. (Box 28, Folder 20)
    - "G", 2006. (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - General Assembly LAS(es), 2001. (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - General Assembly Session, 2002. (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - General Assembly Session Information, 2000. (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - General Assembly Session--Legislation (Henderson), 2001. (Box 24, Folder 27)
    - General Assembly Session--Legislation (McPhie), 2001. (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - General Information/Marketing Plan, 1997. (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - General Records Retention and Disposition Schedule, July 19, 1999. (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - G-Form Information, A2004. (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Gifts from Senate Employee Fund, 1997. (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Governor Jim Gilmore State Employee Town Hall Meeting--Annandale, September 24, 1998. (Box 15a, Folder 5)
    - Governor Jim Gilmore State Employee Town Hall Meeting--Norfolk, September 24, 1998. (Box 15a, Folder 2)
    - Governor Jim Gilmore State Employee Town Hall Meeting--Richmond, September 25, 1998. (Box 15a, Folder 3)
    - Governor Jim Gilmore State Employee Town Hall Meeting--Roanoke, September 23, 1998. (Box 15a, Folder 4)
    - Governor's Commission on Efficiency in Government, 1996. (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Governor's Sports Leagues, 1992-1993. (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Graphic Artists, 1996. (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Grievance Hearing Brochures, June 1997. (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Grievance Procedures Brochure Orders, 1997. (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Grievance Procedures Brochure Orders, 1998. (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Grievance Procedures Brochure Printing, 1997. (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Grievance Procedures Brochure Printing, 1998. (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Grievance Procedure Bulletin no. 3, 1997. (Box 24, Folder 28)
    - Grievance Procedures Bulletins, n.d.. (Box 18, Folder 64)
    - Grievance Procedures Copies, July 1, 1992. (Box 18, Folder 65)
    - Grievance Procedures Correspondence, 1992. (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Grievance Procedures Correspondence, 1995-1999. (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Grievance Procedures History, 1970's. (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Grievance Procedures: Outlines, Interpretations, and Correspondence, 1989-1992. (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Grievance Rulings Correspondence, 1979-1986. (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Gubernatorial and Administrative Correspondence, 1993. (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Guides to Virginia Facilities, 1990. (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Gustafson, Christine, (Draft Letter), 1999. (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - "H", 1997. (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Hammond Commission Meeting--Marion, Virgina-Information File, November 9, 1998. (Box 20, Folder 31)
    - Handbook for Grievance Panel Members, 1990. (Box 28, Folder 16)
    - Handbook for Hearing Officers, 1995. (Box 28, Folder 15)
    - Handicap Survey Form (Certifications and Codes), 1980. (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Handouts for New Training, 1995. (Box 18, Folder 66)
    - Hatch Act, October 1975. (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - HB 222, 2002. (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - HB 450, 2002. (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - HB571--Grievance Procedure Decisions of Hearing Officers, 2000. (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - HB 776, 1994. (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - HB 818, 2002. (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - HB 959 (Del Barlow), 2004. (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - HB 1015, 2002. (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - HB1177--Dept. of Employee Relations Counselors: Grievance Procedure, 2000. (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - HB1544--State Grievance Procedure: Unfair Performance Evaluations, 2000. (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - HB 1917, 2002. (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - HB 1965, 2003. (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - HB 1966, 2003. (Box 29, Folder 3)